Hello friends, I am once again
heartily welcome you to my YouTube channel Stock Trading Techniques.
Friends, today again I have activated Bank
Nifty and am
sharing with you what possibilities are there for 15th September related to it.
You can compare today's results with my video
which I discussed with you on Friday, it is
in the depression box below, you can use it with that,
so let's go, I am recording this video,
at 5:35 pm, in that time zone
Nifty index is only future, the rate is
coming, a Le Dori pattern of 1147 has been created
and the closing has come above a crush support which is
around 1148 that is
1375, as long as the price is turning upwards,
we do not need to think much downwards,
but because there are 2 upper spots
where the resistance is
1151 5150, until the
price does not cross these and goes up, we cannot be very
positive.  Look, I have been
mentioning to you for many days, see the straight
line going upwards and this is a register above,
we can call it on the side
in comparison, but
yes, the moving average is all
closing above the moving average, so now
we will not think too bearish, but as soon as
11375 is tracked for some reason, then we will be
free, then you do not have to think
that your trading strategy is such that as soon as 11375 is broken, you should go for it, for
how many points you have to take
your position for profit, that is up to
you, the stop loss,
what percentage of which level you have to take, that is also
up to you, but the
price that is going to be shot is 11375, for the bank we will
look above 11475, we will place a stop loss of 19, the
target will be 115, 1545, 602, now let's talk about
Nifty Bank,
and today, Nifty Bank's
closing, which we can say is of the active bank, has
come on the low side, as much as in the morning
Abhijeet did one on the whole and lots of
Closing: You will have to keep an eye on 2160.
If tomorrow it opens flat to negative,
then you can take a
shot by placing a stop loss around double 2a 80.
Two lineage 6
is for more than 80 to 90 and we will start thinking when the
price crosses 2280 and goes up. We will
not generate any trading interest in between.
Now let us talk about the good Nifty Bank
shares like HDFC
Bank. HDFC Bank has been having a relationship with bread pizza for many
days and as soon as I
got the signal, I also generated it on Baring's website
and I watched yesterday's video
and if you look, I had targeted 1057, it got
cut today. If tomorrow
we open flight mode settings, then
you can keep a stop loss here and target 11057. It
is 1028. And if this momentum changes a little,
but the momentum acts, if it changes, then
you can take a shot by placing a stop loss here and placing a stop loss of 1058.  You
can buy, the target market is near
1290.
Now let's talk about ICICI Bank, it is
not about
Axis Bank.
Look, the closing given by Axis Bank today is on the
lower side, it is not a good closing,
they are on the reserve, so we will also go to the website by
placing a stop loss of Rs. 1000. If we
open the flight, it will probably
reach negative, then there is no problem.
Start trading with a flat stop loss for the target of 5416. The change or momentum has
reversed a little bit, right now it will be very difficult to cross 453.
Above that, we will take a
position in this bank if it is
not there before that.
Now let me talk to you about Kotak
Mahindra Bank. Kotak Mahindra Bank,
look at my target today, I had
given you a target of 38k and I have given you a target of many days ago.
Look, I had set a target of 129, after all,
how many days ago was that set
and see how well it did. When I
shifted, I had said that day also that
we will take a turn for the reading and see, from there
we came down by almost 200 points,
so can you take a position in this bank from here?  We should
not bike, we have not received the signal from the downside yet,
yes if we cross 1298 then
you can shoot by placing a stop loss of 130,
target for 1238, if the
momentum has reversed a little somewhere, then you will find an opportunity in it, then
place the same stop loss in it and sit in the bag, in this
you can get a small follow up target of 1350,
but
both the trend and momentum are negative, so you should
generate a position on the negative side only,
Axis Bank Pack Husband is in a negative
territory, Hero became 3X, I have
talked to you on this, now I will talk about
any other stock,
Indus Bank was above,
Indus Bank, see, this closing is fine
in comparison to other banks, it is fine now it has
broken its two moving waves, if not
much, then tomorrow if we open flat
to negative then you should
shoot by placing a stop loss of 360, the target will be for
North 575 and if it goes below that then
In this case, there will be targets hanging on
your side, right now there is no sign of it anywhere near it
because the trend is still negative.
Now let me talk to you about the
fact that the fact is that the secret of the IS chief is
ICICI Bank. So,
today's closing of the bank is
around 364 and recently it has set a target of 350. So,
I will tell you about my
targets in this, I have already
discussed with you, let me try to
set one more target, there is a problem in some charts, let me try to set the
target around 39, that is a
good problem,
Om Shri, let me tell you that the
targets seen around 350 in this,
if we want to go downwards then you should
assume that
we can see prices towards 5556
and on your side, when we
cross 375 now, then we will see whether
we have to create a position of the bank above 375,
so now let me talk to you  Also,
what does HDFC show us?
All my targets in SBI have been achieved, which I have been
telling you for many days that it will touch
1735. And today,
it has touched that first 1735 and
this is the third time in the last four-five months. It
touched this advanced powder,
after that it touched it on August 3rd and today,
see, it took some time in September. On which
base was I telling you that you should see this,
this is a gap of around 3240 points,
which it had not filled till now, which it had not filled since the
opening,
hence I am saying that now perhaps we can
see 167,500 price in the stock
and after that a rally can continue.
Now it is on the side, so
now let's see if it comes back from here, if it
comes down here once, then if tomorrow we
open flat to negative, then you can
put a stop loss of 1735 and sort it out
for the target of 1675.
Not far from here, if anyone wants to
see a small momentum reversal and
wants to take a strategy, then by
keeping a stop loss of 1735, if the opening is flat to positive,
then you can bank on the target
of 170 for seven five. Right now the time
is negative and the momentum is also negative, so if
you take this trend ahead of the trend and momentum, then
the chances of incurring losses are high. So
now let us talk about
Reliance.
After two days of decline, Reliance has consolidated a bit today
and is in a slight correction mode. The
closing theme is around 20.
So from here, if we slide into tomorrow,
let's say if we
open negative, then you can take this stop loss
and shoot for the 20 target.
If Nifty has to
come down for any reason, then selling will be seen in this topic.
Today, we have folded ourselves a bit due to the IT sector. Otherwise,
we can move downwards.
If Reliance
participates, then bank.  It is not
possible now because it
will consolidate a bit here. Now, one trick which
I have not talked about is that of State Bank or State
Bank of India,
you should look at the closing of State Bank of India,
after 205, the last losing came, that is,
we closed around 198,
breaking that, we have closed below it as well and if
someone wants to take a view, then
you can take a shot by putting a stop loss of 203
for the target of 197, ah yes, if
you
cross the hanging key, if it crosses 2320, then the
target of 206 will be very easy
and if you cross 206, then a
rally of 20 to 25 points will look very good, so as
long as the trend is negative, the
momentum is negative, then we take a hit on the negative side, that is,
if tomorrow we open flat to negative, then take a
shot with a stop loss of 2 to 3 rupees,
I have
told you the lower target of 197, so
friends,
I want to let you all know that Nitya Benefits
Rating  I post this video and tell you
that you can like it in the neck setting session,
price it with my video
and the results will be in front of you, they will be very
positive, good results and if you
like the video then like my video,
share it and subscribe to the channel
and also do not forget to press the bell icon button, with
this I take leave from you, I will
come in front of you again with a new video, till then thank you, do you want
it